

## CONTACT



+375 (44) 511-11-79



vitaliybyaniskov@gmail.com



GitHub



LinkedIn



Telegram

#### **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2021

Gomel State University name after F.Skorina Software developer

#### **SKILLS**

PHP, OpenCart, Laravel, 1C-Bitrix

MySQL, Redis

JavaScript, JQuery

HTML, CSS, SCSS

Docker

**GIT** 

## **LANGUAGES**

English (A2) Russian (Native)

# **Aniskov Vitaliy**

# PHP developer

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a developer with over three years of experience in commercial development, primarily working as a full-stack developer:

- **Backend:** PHP, OpenCart, 1C-Bitrix (a little), Laravel (a little).
- Frontend: JavaScript, JQuery, CSS, HTML, SCSS.

I'm constantly developing and striving for high-quality, extensible and understandable code.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

## KSK (Homel, Belarus)

01.03.2022 - until today

Software developer

#### **Technologies:**

- PHP, Opencart and Laravel (a little)
- JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS
- Codeception (test), Xdebug, Xprof
- PHPStorm, Navicat, Insomnia, GIT

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Development and maintenance of the website https://ksk.by
- Creating modules, libraries, individual pages, filters, and other functionalities in OpenCart
- Frontend development using CSS, HTML, JavaScript, jQuery
- Integration with various REST APIs: YouGile, Yandex Maps, bplanner (3D kitchen planner), etc
- Writing SQL queries and optimizing them with EXPLAIN
- Debugging code with Xdebug and Xprofile for PHP, as well as using browser developer tools for Frontend
- Writing tests using the Codeception framework
- Developing parsers using PHPQuery
- Working with Laravel to create services and REST APIs

## **Media Line Group (Homel, Belarus)**

01.11.2021 - 01.03.2022

#### Software developer

#### **Technologies:**

- 1C-Bitrix, PHP
- JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS
- REST API

# **Responsibilities:**

- Outsourcing, development, and technical support of websites on 1C-Bitrix.
- Development of components in 1C-Bitrix.
- Developing parsers for unloading goods from docx, xml, csv, as well as web sites.
- Working with various APIs: Google Tag Manager, Google Maps, Google Analytics.
- Administration of 1C-Bitrix.

#### Homselmash (Homel, Belarus)

2011 - 2020

Foreman / CNC Machine Adjuster "MAZAK QTN 250""

- Foreman (2019-2020): working with documentation, managing personnel, overseeing production processes
- CNC Machine Adjuster (2011-2019): setting up machining centers for part fabrication, writing programs, quality control of finished products